Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The royal capital was thrown into chaos by marauding elves who had possessed the bodies of magic knights.
Leopold and the Crimson Lion Kings found themselves battling a formidable elven foe who had taken control of their vice-captain, Randall.
Just then.
From now on, I won't allow anyone to stand in my way.
Though I may have lost my arm, though flames may scorch my body, as long as there are people waiting for me.
The captain of the Crimson Lion Kings, Vuegolion Vermillion, will press on!
You fought well, Leo. I'm proud.
I can't believe you're here!
As head of the Crimson Lion Kings, and as your older brother, I will be bested no longer!
At long last, Vuegolion had awoken from his slumber, with the mighty Fire Spirit Salamander at his side.
Meanwhile, at the eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout...
Ah!
Run along home now, children!
But captain!
Children, but Captain!
Marilyona Vermillion prepared to fight Raya and his underlings on her own.
Squire and the rule Theta 응게Dry and fight
だから待って、待って、待って、待ってって、置いてかないでいてよ
今すぐStry away TATтакa would try again
だから待って、待って待って 同じ場所にいたいよ
Oh
So you want to stay here and slow us down so they can run back with their tails between their legs
You seem like a benevolent leader madam royal
You don't understand a thing do you I?
Sent those novices home because they were getting in my way slow you down. Don't make me laugh
I wanted the chance to obliterate all of you personally
You want to obliterate us, huh?
That's the best joke I've ever heard
You should be able to understand the massive gap in our fighting potential
Sorry miss high and mighty the anti-magic kids ours whether you like it or not
Those swords and grimoire of his every bit of it is property of the real licked
I've been hearing an awful lot of big talk from you time for action
If it's the rookie you want you'll have to go through me
Five against one good enough odds for you
The captain's tough, but not even she can hold her own against all those enemies at once
Come on. We have to go help her
No way stupid we're leaving what you can't just abandon her like that at this rate
She won't make it out alive
And if we go waltzing back in there without a solid plan then none of us are getting out alive
You don't even have magic so you've got no idea how powerful these body snatchers are
Do you seriously think I wanted to let a royal save my neck?
The point is running away is our best shot at somebody surviving this
She was strong to make that choice
So don't let it all be for nothing runt
I'll cast wing magic
Angel wing magic
You expect to emerge victorious in a fight against us my you humans have gotten awfully impertinent while we've been asleep, haven't you?
I believe I said less talk more action
All right, if that's what you want, then I say we should make this quick and easy
Yes, unlike you greedy self-serving humans
We elves are connected to others of our kind by a common bond that can never be broken
So try as you might your pitiful attacks won't put a scratch on any of us
Wing magic
Angel flapping
There really are too many
Picture magic
Subterranean giant's iron arm
You may be strong, but you won't be able to burn this big fella so easily
That grazed me have my senses been dulled it feels like my attacks have been toned down as well
What's wrong?
Snow magic
Phantom snow garden
This technique can weaken the senses of everyone in the area
It doesn't have any effect on elves however, so it puts us at an even greater advantage
Aren't you clever?
I must say for a human you sure know your way around mana
Still it's only a matter of time before you're defeated for good
You've got a lot of nerve challenging the woman who was twice your captain
Ruben
My name isn't Ruben. I am Rosa
Besides, I'd never align myself with such a brute
Is that right?
You're finished!
And I won't hold back
Sandstone magic
Variable hardness prison
I hope you die in there
It's over
What a happy ending
You got that right
It can't be
And to think you were a member of the Crimson Lion King
Which means it's only fitting that you die
By my fire
What's this strange feeling?
This body's instinctively afraid of her
Never again
Will I allow a friend to be murdered
Farewell, Madam Royal
Raya!
What's wrong?
You're here to kill humans, right?
Well, sorry, but it turns out you missed one
This woman
It's like she's immortal
You've started this fight
Now finish it!
There's this fight
You know something?
You're kind of a pain
Haha
I'm alive.
A nice try.
Wow, that is pretty impressive.
How is it possible you're still standing after the beating you just took?
Look, I'll get up as many times as it takes, until all you monsters are dead!
Don't you have the sense to know it's over? Just stop!
Yeah, you're right. Once I cast my strongest spell, it will be over.
Monazone.
Full release!
What? She's not done?
What is that odd sensation? It stinks!
And the snow smell I used. It's melting away.
Flame magic!
Kalinostratium Curvatore!
Can do something else?
Ow!
No! She hurt me!
Despite how much power I used to soften the blow.
How can a human be that powerful?
Five against one, and somehow she still gave us a run for our money.
Yep. I should have known.
That chick's either fearless or crazy.
She can't win. The question is how long she'll hold on.
Well...
You want more?
I'm shocked. You sure you're human?
Don't be shy. Come get me, cowards.
Out of magic. Too weak to move. Yet she still refuses to surrender.
Now you're really starting to freak me out.
We might as well put her out of her misery.
I say we kill her right here and now.
Sounds good to me.
And we'll make sure she goes out with a bang, too.
Copy light magic.
Snow magic.
With wing magic.
And picture magic.
Sandstone magic.
Let's even the odds a little bit.
His idea.
You came back, morons.
This is a whole new level of stupid.
She sacrificed her life so you could run.
And you geniuses blew it.
Compound magic.
Elements of quintet attack.
Now you can all die.
Together.
The point is, running away is our best shot at somebody surviving this.
She was strong to make that choice.
So don't let it all be for nothing, runt.
Maybe so, but it's not fair that she made that decision all on her own.
Because if you ask me, the best thing is for all three of us to survive.
You're even denser than I thought, shorty.
Those people aren't just tough.
They're freaks of nature.
Even your dark anti-magic form won't do us any good.
I know.
And besides, that form is attracted to large amounts of magic power, which means it wouldn't
be the best thing for getting us further away from them.
All right then, why the hell are you fighting me tooth and nail over this?
You got some sort of grand plan?
Well, no, not exactly.
Oh, that's right!
Your magic!
The spell that doubles an attack and reflects it.
Huh?
We'll wait till all five of them cast a spell at the same time.
You can knock it right back in their faces!
You actually think they'll all do something at once?
That'd be some convenient timing, smart guy.
Well, what do you know?
The little runt called it.
To be fair, it's only because the captain's last move forced him into a corner.
He's not fazed at all by the strength of our spell.
I'll double him with my counter trap.
But even two times the amount of power won't be enough to break through their defenses.
Unless...
He finished!
He's aiming at the king?
Nice shot!
He doubled it, then doubled it again!
Quadruple it!
He's aiming at the king.
Wow...
Call me crazy, but it looks like the half pine was accidentally brilliant for once.
Well, hope this works!
Damn it.
I whipped up an improvised magic circle, but it's too sloppy to reflect anything!
Here we go!
Now we get out of here!
We made it!
See? I told you we could all survive this thing!
There's no way you could've known for sure that would work out in our favor.
So don't you go get in a big head!
I swear, one of these days all of that good luck is gonna run out!
Well, when that day comes, I guess you'll have to come save me!
You wish!
Gotcha!
I'm not gonna let you get away!
In fact, I think it's time for you to come along with us to see Lit!
That grimoire and those swords belong to him, and I'm sure he'd like them back now!
Great!
Now what?
Zora!
You take care of the captain!
You serious?
I promise you I'll come back alive, okay?
Go ahead without me!
Are you crazy?
What happened to your big speech about everybody surviving together?
You better make it through this in one piece, or you're dead to me!
You understand?
You stupid kid!
My friends. My teammates. What's wrong? Klaus. Hammond. You know.
Sorry. To whom are you speaking?
You, of course.
Don't use that familiar tone. You should know. We aren't your teammates or friends.
What are you saying?
She's royalty.
Indeed. It appears that way. Humans destroyed the elven people. We will never forgive you.
I should focus on defense for now.
Hmm.
Plant recovery magic. Princess healing flower rope.
Don't bother.
I'm not finished with you.
Hmm.
Better. Yes. I much prefer this look on you.
They're not who they were before. Their magic and their personalities are completely different now. Even you know.
He's awfully quiet. I don't think he's fully awakened to his true identity yet.
Perhaps. But no matter. He should understand who he is in due time.
I said hold still. What a pain.
Asta. Hey.
Mimosa.
Thank goodness.
Are you okay?
Who did this to you?
Just a sec. I'll get you down.
Wait.
We will not allow you to rescue a descendant of criminals.
That's Klaus.
And that chubby guy from the Golden Dawn.
Seriously? You guys too?
This sucks.
So the others are acting the same way?
Oh no!
Cut it out!
I don't want to fight my friends!
Just wake up!
Why are you...
What?
No.
Wait.
How can...
There's no way this is really happening.
I don't believe it!
Mario!
You're not!
One, two, one
I don't need no money. I don't need no魔力は要らない
自力で挑んだミラクル起きること願い
魅力ながら1ミリずつビリビリ切り込んでく
世界を巻き込んでく
My disabilities, my ability
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー
どうしても自らを見失って嫌いになって
負けそうになったら
Just cry out loud
傷つく音に 傷つく音に
立ち向かう勇気へと導いてく
Our treasure
裏切らないのは最高にThere is love
かざしたちが光が生きる treasure
That's for failing
Your turn
Mera Leona, Mera Leona, Mera Leona, Mera Leona
Mera, Mera
How embarrassing
We're sorry for messing up, Captain
Could you show us how to say it?
Are you infants?
Listen closely
ManaZone
Full Release
Okay
Mayo
That's wrong
I failed
What gives?
You know
Don't tell me you're a bad guy now too
What about the promise we made?
Black Clover
Page 100
We won't lose to you
My magic is never giving up